Contact

myersml86@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/leann-myers-76b822131 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Management
Healthcare

<u>Electronic Medical Record (EMR)</u>

Certifications

Nurse Executive, Advanced NEA-BC Leadership Delaware Fellowship

Publications

Managing the Aggressive Child: A Toolkit for Safe Care

LeAnn Myers

Director of Quality Improvement

West Grove, Pennsylvania

Summary

Experienced Director of Quality Improvement with a demonstrated history of working in ambulatory & the health care industry. Skilled in Healthcare Information Technology (HIT), Electronic Medical Record (EMR), Ambulatory, Process Improvement and Healthcare Management. Strong Nursing Executive with an MSN in Executive Leadership from Wilmington University.

Experience

Westside Family Healthcare
Director of Quality Improvement
July 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month)
Wilmington, Delawre

Nemours

6 years 5 months

Director of Clinical Operations & Quality Assurance May 2019 - July 2019 (3 months) Wilmington, Delaware, United States

Clinical Operations Director December 2014 - May 2019 (4 years 6 months)

Wilmington, Delaware

Nursing Manager

March 2013 - December 2014 (1 year 10 months)

Wilmington, Delaware, United States

The Children's Hospital of Philadelphia 3 years 8 months

Lead Nurse

August 2009 - March 2013 (3 years 8 months)

Coatesville, PA

Registered Nurse

August 2009 - March 2010 (8 months)

Coatesville, Pennsylvania, United States

Education

Wilmington University

MSN, Nursing Administration · (2014 - 2017)

West Chester University of Pennsylvania Bachelor's degree, Nursing Science · (2011 - 2012)

Delaware County Community College
Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2005 - 2009)